Hello.
こんにちは
Oh, that's cute.
あら、かわいいっすね
It started to look like Hawaiians.
ハワイアンズっぽいとなっちゃった
Have you started working part-time?
バイト始めた?
No, I haven't started.
いや、始めてないんですよ
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
How have you been?
元気してました?
yes.
はい
It's cute.
かわいいね
Hey, I'd like to hear it on the album.
ねえ、ちょっとアルバムで聞きたいんだけど、
various.
いろいろ
How old are you now?
今何歳だっけ?
I'm almost 19 years old.
もうすぐ19歳
Oh, now I'm 18 years old.
お、今だ、18歳
Oh, it's almost here.
あら、もうすぐか
How have you been lately?
どうですか、最近
What do you think?
どうですか?
I went back to my hometown.
実家に帰省しました
Oh, where is your parents' house?
あら、どこだっけ、実家は?
BA in Hokkaido.
北海道のBA
Ah, Hokkaido.
あ、北海道だね
I see, what did you do when you returned home?
そっか、実家帰って何か何したの?
What did you do?
何した?
I had shrimp.
エビをいただきました
Did you eat shrimp?
エビ食べたの?
Was it delicious?
美味しかった?
pretty.
かなり
You're nervous.
緊張してるねえ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
yes.
はい
I'm still not used to it.
まだ慣れてないもんね
Okay, this room.
いいでしょ、この部屋
Yeah, amazing.
うん、すごい
Surrounded by fish.
お魚で囲まれて
Feel Hokkaido.
北海道を感じる
feel?
感じる?
yes.
はい
There's a shrimp shop, but I haven't seen it for a while.
エビ屋ね、ちょっといないけどね
Is that something? Are you a college student now?
何かあれだっけ、今大学生だっけ?
How old are you?
何年生?
1st year student.
1年生
How is school?
学校はどう?
School is a tough day.
学校は大変毎日
hard?
大変?
study?
勉強?
Studying.
勉強が
勉強がね
You have a dream, right?
なんか夢があるんだよね?
be.
ある
What was that?
何でしたっけ?
band.
バンド
yes.
はい
You want to be in a band?
バ ンドやりたいんだっけ?
This will be a preview text.
試写文になる
oh.
お ー
It's not a preview of seafood.
海鮮の試写文じゃなくて
Oh, no, it's the real thing.
あ、違う、本番なの
I don't know which one is the actual one though.
どっちが本番なのかわかんないけど
Girls band...
ガールズバンドの...
A famous one.
有名なやつ
I did my best.
頑張ったよ
I'd like to go see a live performance.
ライブ見に行きたいんだけどさ
please.
ぜひ
I couldn't find anything.
全然見つけられなかった
They're doing it in Shibuya, right?
渋谷でやってるでしょ?
yes.
はい
copper?
どう?
What are your activities?
活動は?
Junpu One Punch.
順風ワンパンです
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Are the members getting along well?
メンバー間仲いいの?
Yes, we are good friends.
はい、仲いいです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I think it's really cute like this.
こんなね、やっぱ可愛いとね
It's okay to be cute.
可愛さも大丈夫だね
No, I don't need a band.
いや、いらないですよ、バンドは
Don't need it?
いらない?
yes.
はい
There is.
いるよ
Don't you need it?
いらないか
Have you had sex recently?
最近エッチした?
I haven't.
してないです
from.
から
Really?
本当に?
yes.
はい
So aren't you a little horny?
じゃあちょっとムラムラしてない?
no.
いや
Well, it's WoshiWoshi.
まあ、ウォシウォシです
Do you have sex alone?
一人エッチとかするの?
Not much.
あんまり
Not much?
あんまり?
yes.
はい
Do you want to do it for a while?
ちょっとする?
Well then.
じゃあ
It's hard to say.
なんとも言えないですね
You want to do something that feels good, right?
気持ちいいことしたいんでしょ?
I've been feeling a little horny lately.
ちょっと最近ムラムラしてると思って
I'm calling a technician today as well.
ちょっと今日もさ、テクニシャンを呼んでるんですよ
Hey technician.
ちょっと テクニシャン
I wanted to be a member of the band, too.
バンドのメンバーになりたくて、私も
What position do you hold?
どこポジション入ってますか?
Ah, castanets.
あ、カスタネットが
Does it have castanets?
カスタネット入ってる?
happy.
嬉しい
I want to hit it rhythmically.
リズミカルに叩きたいと思います
I want to become a member.
メンバー入りたいです
Now, with maracas.
じゃあマラカスで
With maracas.
マラカスで
With a stick.
スティックで
amazing.
すごい
It's called Eight Beat.
エイトビートっていう
amazing.
すごい
I might really hate it.
めっちゃ嫌かも
It's almost there.
もうそこらへんで
Ah, I touched it.
あ、触った
Now that I've touched it.
触った今
No, I haven't touched it.
いやいや、触ってないですけど
It's a desire.
欲求だ
You look like you're from a southern country.
南国の格好してるんですね
Is that how you usually feel?
普段そんな感じ?
that's right.
そうです
It's summer.
夏なんで
I'd like to see the whole thing with the ocean in the background.
海をバックにちょっと全身見たいんだけど
How tall are 4 castas?
カスタ4頭身長ある?
Maybe.
もしかして
yes.
はい
Vice 13.
副13
It's just two aliens.
ちょっと宇宙人2人なんで
It might be the biggest.
一番大きいかも
What is this?
これ何?
Fuji Rock?
フジロック?
No, this is already a tropical country.
いや、これはもう、南国
Tropical country?
南国?
yes.
はい
No, I thought there were two Fujis.
いや、この、フジが2つあるなって思って
Oh, sure.
ああ、確かに
So let's play some rock music.
じゃあ、ロックを奏でていきましょう
Oh, will you play it for me?
あ、奏でてくれるの?
What kind of situation?
どういう状況
I'm getting too carried away.
調子になりすぎる
First of all, I want to take a good look at the whole body.
全身をね、まずはしっかりと見ていきたいわけですよ
Aren't you hungry?
腹しっきりじゃないですか?
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
That's right, this skirt is quite thin.
あれだね、結構薄いね、このスカート
It's summer.
夏なんで
It's see-through again.
透けてるよ、また
It's bread.
パンって
Oh, that's surprising.
ああ、それはびっくり
That's right, girls who grow up in a place as relaxed as Hokkaido,
あれだね、やっぱ北海道ぐらい大らかな所で育ってる女子は、
You don't really care.
そんなに気にしないんだね
surely.
確かに
It's a little scary.
ちょっとやばい
Janjan.
じゃんじゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Wow, already.
すごい、もう
I don't like it, it's embarrassing.
嫌だ、恥ずかしい
It hasn't even been 5 minutes yet and my butt is showing.
まだあって5分も経ってない、お尻がつり見えてるよ
It's embarrassing, me too.
恥ずかしいよ、俺も
It's plump and warm, like salmon roe.
ぷりぷりもイクラみたいな、ほっぽいな
Looks like salmon roe.
イクラみたい
Luxury arm.
高級アーム
Arm from salmon roe.
イクラからアーム
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Halloween, I got promoted.
ハロウィン、昇格したよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm here.
いたしまう
Are you standing a little closer?
ちょっと近くに立ってる?
Are you standing?
立ってる?
I'm standing.
立ってる
Are you wearing underwear?
下着着てるよね?
I'm wearing it.
着てるよ
着 てる
You can tell just by pressing the bra,
ブラジャー押しでもちょっと分かるよ、
Something.
なんか
I'm sure.
確 かめてるね
I don't know.
分からない
Pinpoint.
ピンポイント
amazing.
すごい
Ching Chin.
チンチン
I wasn't wearing it right now.
今、着てなかった
I'm wearing it.
着てるって
What do you say?
何て言うの?
4 characters.
4文字の
Ching Chin.
チンチン
It's called Chin Chin.
チンチンって言う話なんだね
What do you say?
何て言うの?
There are two of us, so we do these things together.
2人いるからね、2人でこういうことするわけで
What do you mean?
こう いうこと?
various.
いろいろ
amazing.
すごい
cold.
冷たい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Wait, wait.
待って待って
I'm going home wearing this.
私これ着て帰るんだよ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
I'll buy you a new one.
新しいのは買ってあげるから
Doesn't it feel good?
気持ちよくない?
I put it on.
着けちゃいました
Your breasts are big.
おっぱい大きいね
I thought it was big.
大きい大きいと思ってたけど
I'll let you wear it.
着けさせていっちゃうから
What about clothes?
服は?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Don't worry about clothes.
服のことは気にしなくて
We'll take care of it in the end.
我々が最後はとにかくしてあげるから
It's like Mokodo.
モコ道みたい
With plenty of oil.
オイルたっぷりで
I'm wearing pants, though.
パンツマですけどね
I got wet.
濡れた
I'll buy you some pants.
ちょっとパンツマ買ってあげる
amazing.
すごい
But it smells good.
でもいい匂いする
It would be fun to have a band dressed like this.
この格好でバンドしたら面白いじゃん
Still wet?
濡れたまま?
There's no such band.
そんなバンドないよ
It has really sunk in.
し っかり染み込んだね
It's so wet.
め っちゃ 濡れてる
Maybe it's not oily here?
ここだけ多分オイルっぽくない?
It's kind of wet.
なんか濡れ方してる
real?
ほんと?
It's a little sticky here.
ちょっと粘り気あるもん、ここ
real?
ほんと?
I have a constitution that gets wet quite easily.
結構濡れやすい体質
Wet constitution.
濡れた体質
It may get wet easily.
濡れやすいかも
As expected.
さすが
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
This is embarrassing.
これは恥ずかしい
With a lot of renormalization.
ガッツリ繰り込みで
Isn't it Jakeshaney?
ジャケシャニーじゃない?
Isn't this what Asher is all about?
アーシャーでこれ決まりじゃない?
It's dangerous, isn't it?
やばいでしょ、普通に
I'll show you a little bit of it as an introductory bonus.
紹介特典でちょっと見せておくとか
What benefits?
何の特典?
I think it's a privilege for everyone.
みんなに特典だと思うよ
There are pearls in places like this, right?
こんなところに真珠があるじゃないですか
Hey.
ね え
Ah, that's kind of amazing.
あ、ちょっとすごい
Wow, what is this?
すごい、何ですか、この
This isn't oil, it's the way this thread is pulled.
これはオイルじゃないよ、この糸の引き方
It's oil.
オイルだよ
This isn't the way a mekabu pulls the strings, is it?
こんなメカブみたいな糸の引き方じゃないでしょ
I was attacking with disbanded items today.
今日解散物で攻めてたよ
Mekabu.
メカブ
It made a clicking sound.
クチって音したよ
Amazing, I don't miss a single note.
すごい、一音も逃さない
Just one more note.
もう 一音だよ
It's likely to happen.
されそうですよ
difficult.
難しい
A little.
少々さ
It's pretty strong.
結構強いね
You endured it.
耐えたよね
It leaked a little.
ちょっと漏れたよ
Because it was vertical.
縦のりだったからね
It was vertical
縦のりだった
Yo.
よ
I've got big fingers all over my body, so let's say goodbye.
大 指でビシャビシャだからさ、これをさよならしようか
good bye.
さよなら
Let's say goodbye.
さよならしよう
He's finally a person.
やっとる人ですね
My favorite person.
お気に入りやっとる人
favorite.
お気に入り
You're my favorite.
お前お気に入りなのに
It's my favorite
お気に入りな
To the.
の に
You're doing something terrible, right now.
ひどいことしてるよね、じゃあ今ね
terrible.
ひ ど い
I'll lie even once.
一回でも嘘するよ
Yeah, I'm lonely.
うん、寂しい
I feel scared.
怖いさされそう
Eyebrows like this are so fashionable.
眉毛これだけってお洒落なんだよ
It's not fashionable.
お洒落じゃないよ
お 洒落じゃない
It's punk, punk.
パンクだよ、パンク
Kind of positive.
なんか、ポジティブ
There's a microphone here.
こんなところにマイクがある
That's a great mic.
すごいマイクだ
Is it okay to be a little different?
ちょっと変わってていい?
Are you still patient?
まだ我慢?
Good luck!
頑張れね
The pearls of Hokkaido are hitting the nail on the head.
北海道の真珠がガッツリ当てられてるね
Isn't it cute?
可愛くない?
cute.
可愛い
I'm often referred to as Bond.
なんかボンドってよくされて
Ru.
る
It's kind of shiny and embarrassing.
なんか テカテカしてて恥ずかしい
Does it feel clear?
クリア感じる?
Yeah.
うん
This is Crito.
ク リトです
Yeah, I feel it.
うん、感じる
Make it stronger.
もっと強くする
I was really nervous.
すごい緊張した
Let me know if you hit it at a good angle.
いい角度で当たってたら教えて
If I hit it at a good angle.
いい 角度で当たってたら
copper?
どう?
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
Ya ba.
や ば
picture?
え?
Is it embarrassing to have your hair turned upside down?
裏髪られるの恥ずかしい?
Yeah, great.
うん、やば
Because it's stylish and super smooth,
お洒落すごいスベスベな状態だから、
Won't you let me hang out with you?
つるんでくれるんじゃないの?
Ah, I ran away.
あ、逃げた
Are you still calling?
まだかけるの?
I'll still call it.
まだ かける
Plenty of private rooms.
個室たっぷりで
amazing.
すごい
It's already a small path.
もう小道だ
tickles.
くすぐったい
My chest is ticklish.
くすぐったくて胸脇
That's right.
そうなんだよ
I'm just raising it.
上げてるだけ
You didn't expect to be covered in oil wearing hotel clothes.
ホテル着てオイルまみれにされると思わなかったでしょ
I'll run out of clothes.
服もなくなっちゃうし
It was worn.
着られた
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だ
What's next?
次何が来るかな?
Isn't it quite tight?
結構締まり良くない?
It's really tight right now.
今めちゃ締めてるでしょ
It's not tightened.
締めてないよ
No one is touching it now.
今だって誰も触ってないよ
amazing.
すごい
I didn't even tighten it by hand.
手まして締めてない
That's amazing.
すごいね
Maybe if I go like this, I'll be able to get it.
もしかしてこれ、この感じでいくとチンチン取れるね、
this.
これ
I'll put it in later.
後で入れたら
picture?
え?
Haven't you been told?
言われてない?
Do you feel great about the people you've had sex with?
今までエッチした人に、すごい気持ちよまうことか、
Is it tough?
キツよまうことかって
It's a bit narrow.
ちょっともう狭いからさ
Maybe it's small?
狭いかも?
Did your band members tell you that?
それバンドメンバーに言われたの?
There are only women.
女しかいないよ
It's really tight, isn't it?
すごい締まり良いんじゃね?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
this.
これ
This just came in, a little.
これ入ったまんまさ、ちょっと
Is this facing forward?
これ正面向ける?
As it entered.
入ったまんま
real?
ほ んと?
Just like before.
さっきみたいな感じで
This way.
こっち
sit.
座る
Like this.
こうやって
Wait, that hurts a lot.
待って、なんかすごい痛い
Good.
グッ
My legs are so strong.
足グッ
Wait, that's embarrassing.
待って、恥ずかしい
Impossible.
無理
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing, so take it.
恥ずかしいから持って
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Is this embarrassing?
これ恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
It's becoming really cool.
すっごいかっこよくなれてるよ
I can't stop it.
つめねえね
Wait, that's kind of amazing.
待って、なんかすごい
It looks like you're a bit naughty with your hands.
ちょっと手つきすごいやらしいね
Are you used to holding it?
握り慣れてるの?
Maybe.
もしかして
That's not true.
そんなことない
I'm going to make something like this.
何かグッソ作まんまでよ、これ
It's embarrassing so take it out.
恥ずかしいから抜いて
Leave your pussy open the moment you pull out.
抜いた瞬間のおまんこを開いたままにしておいて
amazing.
すごい
It's moving a lot.
めちゃめちゃ動いてる
Mushroom.
きのこ
I don't want to drown it out.
かき消すくないです
Good tightness.
締まりがいい
It has a soundproofing effect.
防音効果あるね
Amazing, for sure.
すごい、確かに
I can do bandration inside this pussy.
このおまんこの中だったらバンドレーションできる
I can be in a band.
バ ンドできる
Amazing, it's a soundproof room.
すごい、防音室だ
Soundproof pussy.
防音まんこ
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい
It's going to be a studio.
スタジオになるね
That's amazing.
すごいわ
Hands, hands.
手よ、手よ
Aren't you going to have two?
2本いってちゃうんじゃない?
It'll get better in a little while.
ちょっともう一気によくなっちゃう
It's impossible.
無理だよ
Wait, what do you mean?
待って、どういうこと?
Things like this.
こういうこと
child
こ
Try licking it while looking at it, looking up at it.
っち 見ながら、上見ながら舐めてみて
It's impossible.
無理だよ
無 理?
Do you want to be filled?
いっぱいされたい?
I want to be filled up.
い っぱいされたい
I'll let you settle down.
おさまにさせてあげるよ
Sit there.
そこ座って
It's not soundproofed at all.
全然防音してない
I'm babbling about this.
ぐちぐち言ってるよ、これ
Isn't it too wet?
濡れすぎじゃない?
Just keep sucking it and watch it.
そのまましゃぶったまま見て
So just stand there.
それでそのまま立って立って
stand, stand
立つ、立つ
Stand while sucking.
しゃぶったまま立つ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
My legs...
足が...
You're numb, aren't you?
しびてるね、あなた
Open normally.
普通に開くの開く
Open this too.
こっちも開く
Open it like this.
開く、こう
Suck on this.
これでしゃぶる
Is it becoming like a private room road?
個室道みたいになっちゃってる?
Are you feeling weak?
力抜けちゃってんの?
That's amazing.
すごいね
This guy is running out of steam.
力抜けてきてるよ、この方
Aren't you pushing it out?
押し出しちゃってるんじゃない?
Because it's a woodpecker.
キツキツオマゴだから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Because it's not in a position like this.
こんな位置しないから
This time next time.
今度こっち
I'm gonna chew, Chu.
チューしちゃうよ、チュー
Without you two, this kind of thing won't stop.
2人いないとね、こういうことはやめないから
Seriously flamingo.
マ ジでフラミンゴ
Flamingo?
フ ラミンゴ?
Battcha is shaking.
バッタッチャ揺れてるね
I came here to earn money.
収入されに来たよ
And, you know, it's Pearl Street.
しかもね、真珠街だから、ほら
It's time for you to become a pearl.
あなたが真珠になる時が来たよ
pearl...
真珠...
What do you think?
どうでしょ?
You'll come again, right?
また来るでしょ?
What about your hands?
手は?
It's turned into a pearl.
めちゃめちゃ真珠になってるよ
Maybe pearls.
真珠かも
copper?
どう?
Do you feel like a pearl?
真珠になった気分?
Wow, it's kind of a bridge.
すごい、なんかブリッジしてる
Are you bridging?
ブ リ ッジしてる?
What is that?
何それ?
It seems like you have a good hand, really.
その手つきやらしいわね、ほんとに
hey.
ね
It feels so good.
す っごい気持ちいい
Can I take this out?
このっぱにさ、出してもいい?
Will it come out?
出る?
Please wake me up.
ひんじん起こしてみて
My boobs came out before I could go.
お っぱい、おっぱい行く前に出ちゃった、
this.
これ
It came out really well.
め っちゃ出てきた
How was it?
どうでした?
Two people, sex with two people.
2人、2人とセックス
It feels like a big deal.
おったいって感じ
It was a flamingo.
フラミンゴだった
Flamingo.
フラミンゴ